ALEKSEI ALIAPKIN

Frontend developer

INFO

PHONE

+7 (916) 426-5709

EMAIL

aaliapkin@gmail.com

SKILLS

Vue is / Vuex

tus. sy tusk
React/Redux
JavaScript
TypeScript
HTML&CSS
Git
C++
SQL
LANGUAGES
Russian
English

CERTIFICATES

Certified Onshape Professional Cad industrial design

PROFILE

Senior front-end developer specializing in Javascript, Vue and jQuery technologies. I performed well, and received rapid career growth to became a team leader. I have a strong mathematical background and significant artistic skills, in particular 3D modeling.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Team lead, ORS

May 2021 - Now

- Shortly after joining became team lead.
- Started to manage team's tasks, perform code reviews
- Take only most complex tasks
- · Perform different activities:
 - DevOps tasks, integration
 - development of internal e2e testing helper framework

Frontend developer, Gridnine systems

Nov 2020 - May 2021

• Finished my tasks timely and received positive feedback for my work.

Financial Reporting specialist, ROSBANK

Jun 2014 - Apr 2019

Achieved employer of the year reward for innovation.

Financial reporting specialist, NOMOS-BANK

Jun 2012 - Oct 2014

 Maintained correct and timely management reporting in accordance with IFRS.

Financial reporting specialist, Russian Standard Bank

Dec 2009 - May 2011

 Maintained and developed complex solutions for management reporting and business planning.

Audit associate, KPMG

Jun 2007 - Apr 2009

 Accomplished financial auditing projects for largest Russian banks.

Full stack developer, Business Partner

Jan 2004 - Jan 2006

 Worked as single full stack web developer in small business.

EDUCATION

Lomonosov Moscow State University

Sep 2002 - Jun 2007

- Graduated from department of mechanics and mathematics. Got specialist degree with honors.
- Specialized in optimization of control of dynamic systems.